It has been said
that magic vanished from our world
a long time ago,
and that humanity
can no longer fulfil its desires
through the power of wishes.
To those who have lost
the wondrous vision of childhood eyes,
submitted here is
the story of a little boy
and a magical Christmas wish
that changed his life forever.
It began in 1985,
in a town just outside Boston.
It was Christmas Eve,
and all the children were in high spirits.
That special time of year
when Boston children
gather together
and beat up the Jewish kids.
Hey, Greenbaum!
It's Jesus' birthday tomorrow,
and you know what
I'm gonna get him?
What?
My fist in your fucking face!
Why would Jesus want that?
Get him!
But there was one child
who wasn't in such good spirits.
Little John Bennett,
that one boy in
every neighbourhood
who just has a tough time
making friends.
Hey, guys, can I play?
Get out of here, Bennett.
Get lost, Bennett!
Get out of here, Bennett!
Yeah, Bennett, get lost.
John longed with all his heart
for that one, true friend
that he could call his own.
And he knew that if he
ever found that friend,
he would never let him go.
Well, as it does every year,
Christmas morning finally came.
All the children
were opening their gifts with holiday glee.
And for little John Bennett,
Christmas Day
brought a very special new arrival.
Wow!
I guess Santa paid attention
to how good you were this year?
Aw! Merry Christmas, John.
I love you!
He talks!
I'm going to name you Teddy.
John became
instantly attached to Teddy.
There was something
about that bear
that made him feel as if
he finally had a friend
with whom he could share
his deepest secrets.
I love you!
I love you, too, Teddy.
You know, I wish you
could really talk to me.
Because then,
we could be best friends forever and ever.
Now, if there's one
thing you can be sure of,
it's that nothing
is more powerful than a young boy's wish.
Except an Apache helicopter.
An Apache helicopter
has machine guns and missiles.
It is an unbelievably impressive
complement of weaponry,
an absolute death machine.
Well, as it turned out,
John picked
the perfect night to make a wish.
Teddy?
Hug me.
You're my best friend, John.
Did you... Did you just talk?
Don't look so surprised.
You're the one
who wished for it, aren't you?
Yeah. I did wish for it.
Well, here I am.
You mean, we get to be
best friends for real?
For real.
Forever and ever?
Sounds good to me.
John was
just about the happiest boy in the world
and he couldn't wait
to tell everyone the good news.
Well, I think
we've had a wonderful Christmas this year.
One of the best.
And I particularly
enjoyed the gift you gave me last night.
Well, my big strong husband
works so hard all year.
I figured you deserved
a little Christmas treat.
I'd call it more
than a little treat.
I think those veneers
just make it a smoother ride for me.
Well, that's
how much I love you.
Seriously though,
that was an outstanding blow job.
Mum, Dad, guess what?
My teddy bear's alive!
Really?
Well, isn't that exciting.
No, Mum,
he's really alive. Look.
Merry Christmas, everybody.
Jesus H. Fuck!
Let's all be best friends.
My God!
John, get away
from that thing. Get over here right now.
But, Dad... Get over here!
Listen to your father! Come here!
Helen, get my gun. Dad, no!
Is it a hugging gun?
Helen, get my gun,
and call the police!
I'm sorry, Mr. Bennett,
I didn't mean to scare anybody.
I just wanted
John and I to be friends.
Yeah, Dad, I made a wish last
night that Teddy was alive
and my wish came true.
My God!
It's a miracle.
It's a Christmas miracle.
You're just like the Baby Jesus.
Well, it wasn't long before
the story of John's little miracle
was sweeping the nation.
Out of a Boston suburb
comes what is, without
a doubt, the most incredible story...
A young boy's stuffed animal
has magically come to life
for, as yet, unknown reasons...
Look what Jesus did!
Look what Jesus did! Look what Jesus did!
Before Long,
Teddy had become a huge celebrity
in his own right.
Hello, Teddy.
You... You are a... You surprise me.
For some reason
I thought you were going to be taller.
I thought you were
going to be funnier.
You...
What are your favourite television shows?
Um, I like Gimme a Break...
Dad. I want a teddy bear.
Hey! What did Daddy
just get you for your birthday?
- A rake.
- That's right.
An excellent rake.
A birthday rake.
So when you clean the yard, you don't have
to pick up the leaves with your hands.
But, Dad. I want the bear on TV.
Donny. Shut up, will ya?
Daddy's making love to New Mummy.
But, Daddy? Go to your hammock!
Do you ever watch this show?
Yeah. When Leno guest hosts.
But through all the fame,
Teddy never forgot
his very best friend, John.
The thunder can't get us, right?
Nope, we're thunder buddies,
and the thunder knows it.
We're totally safe.
Teddy?
Yeah, John?
Do you promise we'll
always be together?
I promise.
Thunder buddies for life.
And that was a promise
that neither one of them ever forgot.
So, where are
John and Teddy today?
Well, let me put it this way.
No matter how big a splash
you make in this world,
whether you're Corey Feldman,
Frankie Muniz, Justin Bieber,
or a talking teddy bear,
eventually, nobody gives a shit.
Do I dare look at the clock?
Look, all I'm saying is
that Boston women are, on the whole,
a paler, uglier sort
than women from the elsewheres of life.
That's bullshit.
What about Lori? She's hot.
No, Lori's from Pennsylvania.
That's not a Boston girl.
They're not that bad.
See, the fact that
you have to say they're not that bad
means that they are that bad.
Did you ever
hear a Boston girl have an orgasm?
Yeah, yeah! Harder! Harder!
God, that was so good!
Now I'm going to
stuff my fucking face with Pepperidge Farm!
Jesus, this is weak.
It's not even getting me high. I got
to have a talk with my weed guy.
It's working for me.
I think it sucks.
I'm going to have a talk with him.
I don't know that you want to go
to a drug dealer with complaints.
No. I know this guy a long time.
I've known him since 9/11.
You remember? I was, like,
"Shit, 9/11. I got to get high."
ls it 9:30? Yeah.
Shit, I got to get to work!
I don't know if I can drive!
It's okay,
I'll drive you. I feel fine.
Fuck! Shit.
Man!
Johnny, I'm sorry,
man. That car just came out of nowhere.
God, is it bad?
Man!
John! May I speak
with you, please?
Shit.
It's all right, go, go, go.
I'll pull out of here.
Hi, Thomas, how are you?
Asshole!
That's my bad.
I was sending a tweet.
John, it's almost 10:00.
I know, sir, I'm sorry.
It wasn't my fault.
What do you mean?
I guess I wasn't
really prepared for a follow-up question.
John, all you got to do
is not fuck up
and you get my job
when I go to corporate next month.
You're the new branch manager.
All you've got to do
is not fuck up.
I realize that. Good.
Glad to hear it.
Because in a month,
my life could be your life.
A cushy, $38,000-a-year
branch manager
who's personal friends
with Tom Skerritt.
Not a bad life, is it?
No.
I'm going to show you
something that I don't like to show people
because I don't want them
treating me differently.
Boom. That's me and Skerritt.
Wow.
Goddamn right, "Wow."
I'm gonna dock you
for dinging the car
and for showing up
late today, all right?
Try and be a little more
responsible tomorrow.
I will, sir, I promise.
I'm not going to
let you down, Goose.
What?
Top Gun.
So?
Tom Skerritt.
I know that.
I don't think of him as an actor anymore.
He's just, like, a guy.
Like, we work...
We worked on my garage two months ago.
Helped me hang a garage door.
You ever
hang a garage door with Tom Skerritt?
No. No.
You ever go miniature golfing
with Tom Skerritt's wife and her kid?
No. You haven't.
Do you ever watch a Bulls game,
Chicago Bulls game
in Chicago with Tom Skerritt?
No. No.
You haven't. All right.
Liberty, fast track,
Skerritt, John.
Thank you, sir.
All right,
here's your keys, your rental agreement,
complimentary map of Boston.
Thank you for
choosing Liberty. Drive safely.
Thanks. Thanks so much.
I heard you got busted.
Jesus, Guy,
you look like shit, man. What happened?
I don't know,
I got fucking wasted last night.
My phone says I texted someone at
3: 15, asking them to beat me up.
And then, at 4:30,
I texted the same person saying, "Thanks."
And you don't remember it?
No, same as last time.
It just seems
kind of gay, doesn't it?
I don't know. Maybe, yeah.
Well, do you think
you're part of some gay beat-up underworld?
Like one of those
gay beat-up clubs or something?
I don't know. I dig chicks, man.
I don't remember any of it.
I was so fucked up.
I might be gay, I don't know.
Do you mind
covering for me for a bit?
I might go lay down in the John.
Hey, buddies.
Where is it hanging?
Hey, Alix, what's up?
You get in the club last night?
I didn't get in because
the bouncer was douche-face.
But I made friends in the line.
That's good, I guess.
Hey, guys, anybody
know a nice restaurant,
like something
where they give out
free bubblegum in the bathrooms?
For what?
Lori and I have been dating
four years tomorrow.
I want to take her
someplace really nice.
Aw, congratulations, John.
You guys have been
going out for four years?
My longest relationship
was like six months
and then she farted
in her sleep.
I'm like, "I'm out of here, man."
I was gone before she woke up.
You're not very tolerant?
Lori ever fart in front of you?
Yeah.
Really? Yeah, many times.
You Italian? No.
Why?
Never mind.
Take her to Benihana.
John, look, don't you
think after four years
maybe she's
hoping for something more than dinner?
Like what?
I don't know, but if it were me,
I'd be expecting a proposal.
Come on, nobody's expecting
anybody to propose.
I mean, marriage isn't...
isn't love enough?
I submit that love is enough.
You can put
the ring in her ass, let her fart it out.
So bad, but so good.
Yeah. It's a study in contrasts.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
I love this part right here.
He's for every one of us!
Stands for everyone of us!
He'll save with a mighty hand.
Every man, every woman, every
child With a mighty flash!
Yeah. Fuck, yeah. Flash! My God.
Hey, by the way,
don't let me forget,
you and I got to
nail down a plan
for the Bruins game
tomorrow night.
No, I can't.
I'm taking Lori to dinner.
For what?
Well, we've been
dating four years tomorrow.
Fuck me. Nice.
Let me ask you something.
You don't think
she's going to be
expecting something big, do you?
What, like anal?
No, like a fucking circular
gold thing on her finger.
Fuck that!
It's been four years, Johnny.
You and me have been
together for 27 years.
Where's my ring?
Where's my ring, asshole?
Where's my ring,
motherfucker? Stop it. Come on!
Put it on my fuzzy finger,
you fuck! Come on!
All right, knock it off!
All right, I'm just saying.
But do you think she might be expecting
me to make that kind of a move?
No, I don't think she is.
And, not only that, it's the wrong time.
It's a terrible idea.
I mean, you got the economy.
You got the credit bubble,
the Supreme Court.
I mean, look at Haiti.
I guess I didn't
think about that.
Well, that's... It's a factor.
Who are you?
Flash Gordon.
Quarterback, New York Jets.
This is
the American fantasy, right here.
A professional NFL player
is called upon to save the world.
Tom Brady could do that.
Tom Brady could do that!
Hey. Hey, sweetie.
Hey, Lori.
Hi. Hi.
What do you got there?
Turkey burgers.
Are we having homosexuals
over for dinner tonight?
Ha-ha. No, just you homos.
Whoa! Whoa!
You kind of just
reworded my joke, but...
How was work?
It was fine.
How's your dickhead boss?
Rex is fine.
He only hit on me once today,
so, it's a good thing.
Hey, Johnny, how about a beer?
A couple of
Charles Brew-kowskis?
Couple of Brew-stoyevskis?
Maybe a Mike Brew-gaslowski?
Perhaps a Tedy Brew-ski?
That's a good one.
You know what, I think I, too,
want a Martina Navrati-brewski.
No, that doesn't work.
Don't ruin it. No.
Bullshit! That totally works.
No, no.
Yeah, it does. It doesn't work.
The name has to have
a "ski" at the end of it
and you just put "brewski" at the
end of "Martina Navratilova," so...
I just thought we
were saying funny names.
No, it has to have
a "ski" at the end of it.
Otherwise,
where's the challenge?
If there's no "ski" at
the end of the root word
then we would
just be idiots saying nonsense.
Hey.
They found the missing hikers.
They did?
Yeah. What happened?
They said they got separated
and one of them
had his foot stuck under a rock
for like, five days.
Wow.
You know,
if your leg got trapped under a rock
I'd chew it off to get you free.
You would?
I sure would.
Is that cannibalism?
No, I think
it's only cannibalism if you swallow.
Yeah, no!
Don't worry about that,
because I don't swallow.
Really? 'Cause
that's not what I heard.
Well, it's not true, okay?
I'm a fucking classy broad.
Yeah.
I can see that.
Listen, speaking of classy,
Ciao Bella is a really
expensive restaurant.
So, we can go
anywhere else tomorrow.
I really don't care,
as long as we're together.
Are you kidding me?
No, no, no. Four years,
we've been going out.
I'm taking you to
the best place in town.
I've been
crapping out room for it for two days.
I mean, I know exactly
what I'm gonna order.
You are so disgusting.
And I love you.
I love you, too.
And you're nasty.
Do you want to get nasty?
You're a nasty girl.
Fucking cocksucker motherfucker!
I don't understand.
Thirty-five years old and you're
still scared of a little thunder.
I am not!
Thunder buddies for life,
right, Johnny? Fucking right.
Let's sing
the thunder song. All right.
When you hear the sound
of thunder Don't you get too scared.
Just grab your thunder buddy
And say these magic words.
Fuck you, thunder
You can suck my dick.
You can't get me, thunder
'Cause you're just God's farts.
Hey, Lori,
can you set the alarm for 11:00 A.M.?
I've got a lot of
stuff to do tomorrow.
Good morning, Lori.
Good morning.
Okay.
You okay there, sweetheart?
You look a little flustered.
I'm fine, I'm fine,
I just didn't have time
for breakfast and the garage was full,
and that's right, my boyfriend
can't sleep through a thunderstorm
without his teddy bear.
I don't understand
why you keep putting up with him.
Yeah, I mean, the guy's 35,
and he's working for a rental car service.
You know, you guys,
it's really not about that.
I don't care about that.
I mean, I'd love him if he was a janitor.
I mean,
he has a huge heart and we laugh a lot.
It's just a bonus that he's
the hottest guy in Boston.
I don't know.
I just wish he would get his life together.
Our life. And he can't.
And, I swear to God,
it is because of that bear.
You should give him an ultimatum.
It's you or the bear.
No, I can't do that.
That would devastate him.
Besides, what if he chose Ted?
Well, hello there.
Sorry if I'm interrupting
any private girl-talk
about Channing Tatum's
index finger.
But, Lori, I need to
see you in my office.
Yeah, the thing is, Rex,
I have a lot of work I need to get to...
This is work, I swear.
Great.
Good luck. Thank you.
He's such an asshole.
Out of control.
He's such a sleaze.
A hundred bucks says
he's showing her the diving team photo.
Check this out.
That's me on
the high school diving team.
We dove the shit out
of that pool that year.
Now, if you look close,
you can see the outline of my root.
You promised me
this was about work.
Lori, why don't you like me?
I'm rich, I'm good-looking,
my dad owns the company.
I have a boyfriend.
I have told you this.
Yeah, the guy with the bear.
But I'm talking about
a mature relationship, Lori.
If we were together,
our babies would be spectacular.
With my top-of-the-pyramid
Caucasian genes and your splash of
dark, beautiful, smoky...
Baltic? Czech?
Goodbye, Rex.
Okay, you're fired. No. I'm not.
Okay, that was perfect.
Would you like me to
wrap your leftovers?
No, I'm good. Thank you.
Actually, could you
wrap just this up for me?
I want to scare
the shit out of somebody.
Sure.
What are you, five years old?
Yeah.
But I read at
a six-year-old level, so...
Sir, and madam,
here is your dessert
and champagne.
Ooh!
Cristal.
It's a special night.
We've been dating for four years.
And hey, all those rich black
people can't be wrong, right?
It doesn't feel like
four years, does it?
No, it doesn't.
You know, you had
no business being out on that dance floor,
but I'm really happy
that you were.
This song is so great.
Yeah.
Chris Brown can do no wrong.
Wow, you can really move.
You like that?
Check this shit out.
My God!
Are you okay?
God, I am so sorry.
No, I'm fine, I'm fine.
Jesus, I am so sorry.
I didn't see you. It was an accident.
Did you hurt your head?
Yeah, my head hurts a lot.
Man. Here,
let me get you some ice.
Sorry, sorry. Does it hurt?
No. It's fine.
Okay, here's a test to
see how much you actually care about me.
You remember that night,
after the club
we went and had late-night eggs
and waffles until about 5:00 A.M.
We watched a movie
on the little TV in the diner.
Name that movie.
Octopussy.
Baby! Gold star.
And, by the way,
my dancing was not that bad.
It was pretty bad.
I have cool moves.
Yeah, so do people
with Parkinson's.
That's not how I remember it.
Okay, how do you remember it?
All right, whatever you say.
Hey Yes?
Here's to four more years.
Okay. You make me happy.
Now, I know
we said no gifts, but...
We said no such thing.
I got you something anyway,
in clear violation of the "no gift" rule.
We had no such rule.
Lori, I've wanted to
give this to you for a long time.
John...
Those are the ones you like, right?
From that kiosk at the mall.
Yeah.
You know, Lori,
someday, there's going
to be a ring in there.
But I want to wait
until I get you something really special.
I just don't have
the money right now.
Look, I'm only saying this
because I love you.
You're not going to
have any sort of career
if you keep
wasting time with Ted.
Jeez, here we go.
Baby, please ask Ted to move out
so we can move on
with our lives.
Lori, look,
he's been my best friend since I was eight.
I was not a popular child.
You have to understand,
I had no friends before he came along.
He's the only reason
I ever gained any fucking confidence.
I could have wound
up like that Asian kid at Virginia Tech,
but I didn't 'cause of him.
So, you know, I'm not
that psyched to just, like, kick him out.
Well, it's good to know
that a talking teddy bear is the only thing
that prevented you
from gunning down your classmates.
But you're no longer eight.
You're 35 years old.
And unless you're
too blind to notice,
he's not your
only friend anymore.
Can we talk about
this another time,
and just enjoy
our anniversary dinner?
Shit, hang on a second.
Now my phone
fell under the seat somewhere.
Can you call it?
Yeah.
Is that my ringtone?
What is it?
'Cause it sounds negative.
No, no, it's from The Notebook.
This is going to take
some doing, I think.
I'll just meet
you upstairs then?
Yeah, I'll be right there.
Lori, hey, you're home early.
What the hell is this?
The ladies and I
were just watching Jack and Jill.
Adam Sandler plays
a guy and his sister, and it's just awful.
It's unwatchable.
But, they're hookers,
so it's fine.
This place is a wreck.
Who are these girls?
Where are my manners?
Lori, this is Angelique,
Heavenly, Cherene, and Sauvignon Blanc.
I love you girls.
You know, somewhere out there
are four terrible fathers
I wish I could thank
for this great night.
What is that?
What is what?
There is...
a shit on my floor.
In the corner, there is a shit!
My God! You know what?
That's probably
what Dierdre was doing over there.
Remember she was crouched
over in the corner for a really long time?
I thought she was
just making a phone call or something.
There is a shit on my floor!
Yeah. Yeah.
She's passed out in the bathroom now.
She seemed like
she was hopped up on something,
but, you know,
mystery solved, I guess, right?
She was taking a shit.
What the fuck?
Who lives here?
I'm coming to get whoever lives here.
You owe me lobster money.
That's my buddy, Johnny.
Not the lobster,
the guy running it.
I found my phone.
What's going on?
Is that a shit?
God, there are some
fucked-up fish out there.
Look at that one.
WASP-y, white-guy fish.
"I married the wrong woman,
and now I lead a life of regret."
Look at this guy.
"I went to New York once
in 1981, and I just did not feel safe."
Ted, you gotta move out.
What?
It's got to happen.
What did I do?
My relationship is at
a very delicate stage, you know.
Lori and I may just need
a little space right now.
Plus, a hooker
took a shit in our apartment.
God! What?
This is so gross!
Don't tell me! I don't
want to hear about it! Did you get it?
No, I didn't get it!
Tell me when you get it!
My God, I got some on my thumb!
No! You can never cook
with that hand again!
My God!
You have to learn to cook left-handed.
This is the most
disgusting thing ever!
Don't! Get it away from me!
Look, that was
a tough night for all of us.
Ted, you mean
everything to me, and so does Lori.
I'm just trying to
find a way to keep you both in my life.
She's making you
do it, isn't she?
Yes.
But that doesn't mean we can't hang out.
We'll hang out all the time.
Yeah, but what about
"thunder buddies for life," Johnny?
I know.
I just don't know what to do, here.
I know it sucks,
but otherwise I'm going to lose her.
And I do love her, Ted.
I know you do, Johnny.
I'll help you get on
your feet out there, I promise.
I know. And we'll
hang out all the time, right?
All the time.
Fuck it. Bring it in. Come here.
Bring it in, you bastard.
Come on.
I love you!
Fuck. Shit, sorry,
that's the thing from the...
The old... Yeah, yeah.
I'm not gay. I know.
And you're not gay,
so we're fine.
We gotta get you a job.
I look stupid.
No you don't. You look dapper.
I don't. I look like
Snuggle's accountant.
Come on, it's not that bad.
John, I look like
something you give your kid
when you tell him Grandma died.
Look, I know it sucks, okay?
But you've got
to make some money
so you can pay for an apartment.
I don't want to work
at a grocery store.
Yeah, but you have no skills.
I told you,
I can totally be a lawyer.
As I said, you would
need a law degree from a law school.
No. No. I'm a special case.
I'm a... I'm a talking teddy
bear, for Christ's sake.
They might make an exception
'cause they'd be all like,
"My God! This bear's so cool."
"He can talk and do stuff.
Let's give him a job."
"Maybe he'll
give us a few laughs around the office."
And then they're like,
"My God! He can deliver."
"He's actually
quite a litigator."
And then they practically have
to give me the Anderson case.
You get the job,
we're celebrating after, okay?
And if I don't get the job,
are we still going to
smoke that pot?
Probably, yes.
Okay, all right.
Good talk, coach, thanks.
All right, buddy, go get 'em.
And don't worry,
I'll do my very best
to get this job that I so crave.
So you think you
got what it takes?
I'll tell you what I got.
Your wife's pussy on my breath.
Nobody's ever talked
to me like that before.
That's 'cause everyone's
mouth is usually full of your wife's box.
You're hired.
Shit.
Well, I am a former celebrity
in a minimum wage job.
This is how the cast of
Different Strokes feels.
All day, every day. Just awful.
They must feel awful.
The live ones must feel awful.
Come on.
It's not that bad, okay?
I got a shitty job,
and I assure you, I am quite content.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to bother you
but my son and I
couldn't help but admire your teddy bear.
Thank you. Thanks.
Yeah. I'm Donny, this is Robert.
I have to say, I've been following
you ever since I was a young boy
and I remember seeing you
on the Carson show.
You were just wonderful.
Yeah, that was
a weird interview.
Ed thought I was ALF, and he kept
muttering anti-Semitic comments.
He thought ALF was
Jewish for some reason.
Have you ever considered
selling the bear?
What? Excuse me?
I want it.
I'm not an "it," pal.
I'm a "he," all right?
I'm sorry, little guy,
but my bear isn't for sale.
See, I've had him
since I was about your age.
He's very, very special to me.
Stand up straight when
you're talking to me.
Why the fuck would he say that?
Sorry, you really shouldn't
swear in front of children.
Look, we're very
interested in the bear.
If you want to make
some sort of arrangement
here's my address
and phone number.
And you can call me
any time, okay?
Will do.
Here it goes, in the really important
pocket for really important stuff.
Okay? Okay.
Okay. See you later.
Come on, Robert.
Take it easy.
What the fuck?
Can you imagine
what that little shit would do to me?
I could totally see him
just taking you down to the basement
and really slowly de-limbing you
while singing some creepy
Victorian nursery rhyme.
My little sixpence
My pretty little sixpence.
Stop it. Knock it off.
I love my sixpence
Better than my life.
Stop it! Fuck!
Why you got to take it to that place?
You took it to a very...
Now it's real. Now it's a real thing.
Come on. Take it easy.
All right, look, let's just find
a better place to get stoned.
I guess this is it?
Yeah. Yeah, I guess so.
First night on your own.
Yeah, first night in
my beautiful new apartment.
It'll be great
when it's furnished.
Yeah, and the guy said
it ain't hardly had no murders in it.
So, that's good.
Okay, so,
if you need anything...
Yeah, I know.
Don't worry, Johnny, I'll be fine.
I know you will.
All right.
Hey there.
Hey.
Hi. Hi.
Listen,
I just want to say thank you.
I know what you did
with Ted wasn't easy,
and I just want you to know
that I love you for it,
and I think
it's a new beginning for our relationship.
Hey, anything for you.
This is all part of the new,
grown-up adult John Bennett,
so you better get used to him.
Really?
Well, you know,
I don't have to be at work
for another 20 minutes.
Well, that's perfect.
Because I'm only
going to need one.
You know what
my favourite thing about you is?
That, even after four years,
you can still surprise me.
To step up and change
such a huge part of your life
just to make your
girlfriend happier...
I don't know,
I guess most guys wouldn't do that.
Well, most guys
don't have you to motivate them.
I know I'm not
a talking teddy bear,
but at least you didn't
have to make a magical wish to get me.
How do you know?
Is that a Flash Gordon ray gun,
or are you just happy to see me?
There we go.
Thank you very much, please come again.
We have a lot more groceries.
Hey, Ellen.
Yeah?
Who's that over there?
That's the new checkout girl.
Don't know her name. Seems cute.
Yeah, very cute.
Do you know what I'd like to do to her?
Something I call a Dirty Fozzie.
Okay, all right,
so that's where we'll draw the line.
Hey, how are you holding up?
I'm all right. I'm just getting
used to things, that's all.
It's going to be all right.
I actually went through
something like this with my last boyfriend.
Really? Yeah.
We were together
for eight months, and I really loved him.
And then he got
deported back to lran,
so I know what
you're going through.
Yeah. So, I guess we both
lost our furry little guy.
We sure did.
Hey, Ted.
Hey, Johnny, what are you doing?
You want to come over
and catch a buzz?
Well, I could
probably stop by after work.
Fuck that. I traded off yesterday
so I got the other shift.
Come on, I'm bored as crap over here.
Just swing by for a bit.
I cannot just ditch work, man.
Look, I'm trying to
get my shit together
and be an adult here,
for Lori's sake.
John, five minutes
and then I'll kick you out, I promise.
Just come over.
I got the Cheers DVD box set
and the guy down
at the store told me
that everybody talks shit
about each other in the interviews.
You'll kick me out in five?
I will kick you out in five.
John, I have to kick you out.
I have so much teddy bear paperwork
I have to get to, it is sick.
What do I tell Thomas?
Just tell him you
don't feel well.
I gotta cut out for a bit.
Lori tried to
break up a dog fight
and I guess she
got hurt pretty bad.
My God!
Yeah, that's the way she is.
She sees trouble and
she wants to help out,
and I guess one of these
dogs clamped his jaws on her forearm
and wouldn't let go
until the fireman showed up
and stuck his finger in his ass.
Jesus.
Yeah, she's pretty shook up.
Up the dog's ass, right?
Yeah, up the dog's,
not the fireman's ass.
I thought the fireman
stuck his own finger up his own ass.
No, I don't think
a firefighter would do that.
Go, take care of it.
Let me know how she is.
Thank you. Go.
Was there cocaine
on the set of Cheers?
Um, let me see,
what's the best way to answer that?
Are there naked dicks
in gay porn?
Yeah. Yeah, there was a...
There was cocaine on the set,
but it was the '80s, man.
You know?
I was the king of the '80s.
I was Ted-fucking-Danson.
More importantly, I was
Sam-fucking "Mayday" Malone.
What was your other question?
Yeah, was I popular?
Are there naked dicks in gay porn?
Yeah. Yeah.
No, I was, I was beloved.
You know,
he's exactly who you want him to be.
He is. He is a man we can
all model ourselves after.
Woody Harrelson.
Smallest dick I've ever seen on a man.
See, that's why
I watch these things.
That's like a cool behind-the-scenes
thing that you wouldn't know.
Hey, listen, try this.
I told my weed guy
to step it up and he gave me that.
What is it?
It's called "Mind Rape."
It's actually pretty mellow.
It doesn't sound very mellow.
Well, he only had
three other batches.
"Gorilla Panic,."
"They're Coming,
They're Coming,"
and something called,
"This is Permanent."
Go on, spark it up.
There you go. You got it.
Nice. Good? Good job.
Yeah. Take pride in that.
You know,
this place looks great.
Thanks, man, it's all IKEA.
Did the whole place for $47.
Nice. Yeah.
How are the neighbours?
You know,
there's an Asian family living next door
but they don't have
a gong or nothing, so it's not too bad.
That's lucky. Yeah, it is.
How's work? It sucks.
You?
You know, not bad actually.
I met a girl. She's a cashier.
No way, that's awesome! Yeah.
Well, we should
fucking double-date, or something.
You, me and Lori,
and what's her name?
White trash name. Guess.
Mandy? No.
Marilyn? No.
Britney? Tiffany? No. No.
Candice? No.
Don't fuck with me on this.
I know this shit!
Do you see me
fucking with you? All right, speed round.
I'm going to
rattle off some names
and when I hit it,
fucking buzz it.
I will tell you. You got me?
All right,
Brandi, Heather, Channing,
Breanna, Amber, Sabrina, Melody,
Dakota, Sierra, Bambi, Crystal,
Samantha, Autumn, Ruby,
Taylor, Tara, Tami,
Lauren, Charlene,
Chantal, Courtney, Misty, Jenny, Krista,
Mindy, Noelle, Shelby,
Trina, Reba, Cassandra,
Nikki, Kelsey, Shawna,
Jolene, Earline, Claudine,
Savannah, Kasey, Dolly, Kendra,
Carla, Chloe, Devon, Emmylou.
Fucking Becky? No.
Wait, was it any one
of those names with a "Lynn" after it?
Yes.
I got you, motherfucker.
I got you. Okay.
Brandi-Lynn,
Heather-Lynn, Channing... Tami-Lynn.
Fuck!
What the hell?
Hey, man, you think you can
open more than one register?
There's, like,
1,000 people here.
There's supposed to be
three registers open.
For God's sakes.
Stick your finger
in the loop of my tag.
You had sexual intercourse
with a co-worker
on top of the produce
that we sell to the public.
I fucked her with
a parsnip last week
and I sold the parsnip
to a family with four small children.
That took guts. We need guts.
I'm promoting you.
You got a lot of problems,
don't you?
All right, Kareem!
You suck, Kareem.
Hello?
Hey, Ted.
Hey there, fella. How are you?
Are you out here all alone?
No, no, I'm not.
You know, you're never alone
when you're with Christ.
So, no, I'm not alone.
Yeah. Me, too.
You know, Robert and I
could give you a very, very good home.
Yeah, I'm pretty happy
where I am.
I just got
a shitty new apartment...
I can offer you
$6,000 in railroad bonds.
Well, you know,
since I just returned
from active duty
in the Civil War
that actually
sounds very appealing.
Wait, I'm sorry.
That was 150 years ago
and I don't give a shit.
Okay.
Teddy, come on, we're going to be
late for dinner with your friends.
Okay, be there
in a second, baby.
As you can see,
my dance card is quite full.
So, I'm going to
have to decline.
Can I just get a hug?
No.
Yeah. No, no.
And it kills me to have to tell you
no, because I'm a people pleaser.
Yeah.
Thank you for
creeping up my night.
And Jesus be with you... Okay.
In Christ.
Who was that guy?
That was Sinead O'Connor.
She don't look so good no more.
See. I was all pissed off
'cause me and my friend Danielle
was supposed to go
skydiving last year,
but then she got pregnant from this
asshole guy, and so we couldn't go.
And I was all upset.
But then she had a miscarriage
and so, we ended up
getting to go skydiving.
And it was so scary,
but it was, like, so much fun.
Hey, well, sounds like
everything worked out then?
I know! You know, it's like God
wanted me to go skydiving, you know?
Jesus.
Or Jesus. Him, too.
Could be him.
Yeah.
How great is this?
The four of us out to dinner.
How long have we been saying
we were going to...
Lori, how you doing?
I haven't talked to you in forever.
I'm good. I'm good.
The company's having
their 20th anniversary party next week.
So, that's something.
Lori's a senior VP
at a big, huge PR firm.
It's not that big of a deal.
Company's turning 20?
So you can bang it,
but you can't get it drunk.
Right? Yeah, she gets it.
She enjoys my humour.
Yeah, Rex is having
a house party
but I'm surprised
John didn't tell you, considering
you two have seen each other every
single day since you moved out.
You know, it's funny,
because whenever Johnny and I hang out
the first item on our agenda is,
"What's going on with Lori?"
So, it's funny that
that didn't come up.
That must have
slipped through the cracks.
Yeah, but we do talk
about you all the time.
Yeah, you remember
the other day, I was saying
how great Lori's
hair always looks.
My God,
it always looks so great!
I always want to
fucking brush it.
Right, Johnny? I say that.
So, Tami-Lynn,
why don't you tell us
a little bit about yourself?
Like, where are you from?
I'm always fascinated
to meet Ted's girlfriends.
What do you mean "girlfriends"?
Was there a lot of them
or something?
No, that's not
what she meant at all. Right, Lori?
Lori, you didn't
mean that. No, no, no.
What I meant to say
was Ted's very handsome
so I'm always
interested in meeting
the lady that can snatch him up.
Did you just call me a whore?
What?
You just worry about your own
"snatch." How about that, honey?
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
What the hell happened?
We're having a friendly meal here.
This was a nice evening.
Don't talk shit to me.
I just asked you a question.
You know,
you're a freaking snob.
You think you're
cool because you work
at some fucking fancy
shit place, whatever.
Okay, take it easy.
Nice, Lori, real nice.
Me? It's not my fault
she can't speak English.
Fuck you!
Just because you're on the business
world and shit you think, what,
everybody should
suck your asshole, or something?
Okay. All right, Tami, come on, honey.
Let's get out of here.
We'll go back to my place
for a couple of vodka and strawberry Quiks.
You know what? Stick your fucking
asshole right up your fucking ass.
How about that? You're lucky I'm in
my fucking restaurant clothes, bitch.
'Cause I'd kick your
fucking ass right now.
I gave birth once, bitch.
I could kick your fucking ass.
And you better never show your
face around Quincy, you hear me?
Okay, come on. Ever!
I didn't know
you had a baby. Ls it alive?
What a cunt.
I hate that word!
What? That word.
It's so sharp,
it's like an electric sword
slashing everything in its path.
Why would you say that?
You didn't exactly
stand up for me.
I'm trying to walk a line, here.
I want to be fair
to you and to him, you know?
I think you're being
a little more fair to him.
Come on.
You know, your boss called this
morning asking me how my arm was.
Yeah, because of that dog fight
that I tried to break up.
If I had to make a guess
I would say that
you made up some bullshit excuse
to get out of work
to go to Ted's.
Now, am I right?
I made you out to be a hero.
You know what, John,
we asked Ted to move out
so we can give ourselves
a chance without him.
You're not giving
anything a chance
if you keep blowing off
work to get high with your teddy bear.
You're right.
I've been getting
stoned too much. I know that.
I've been bumming
around with Ted too much. I know that, too.
You give me one more chance,
I promise I can fix it.
John, I need a man.
Not a little boy with a teddy bear.
I know, done. Man.
Right here, in front of you, all right?
Look at these pecs.
These are man pecs.
Look at the hair
on my upper lip. That's man hair.
I just farted.
That was a man fart.
Fine, John, but this is,
I swear to God, your last chance.
Trust me. I love you.
All right, I love you.
I love you so much.
You won't be sorry, I swear.
Did you really just fart?
Yeah, but I pushed it
that way with my hand.
I wonder who it's
going to hit first.
So, if I told him once,
I told him a million times
these numbers do not add up.
Who did this to us?
God damn it!
I'm here on business!
All right, here we go.
I'm really glad that you came.
Me, too. Yeah?
Is it okay if I
kick your boss's ass?
That won't affect
your workplace chemistry, will it?
Please play nice.
For you, I will.
Thank you. Anything.
There she is.
I was worried you weren't coming.
Hey, squirt, how you doing?
Where's your bunny rabbit?
He's a bear.
Got it. My God!
This house is fucking huge!
I know.
Try not to get lost. Come on in.
Wow! Here are the ladies.
Look at you guys.
You guys look amazing.
A little heavy
on the eye make-up, but pretty good.
Thank you, Rex. Thank you.
You guys know
Lori and Jim, right?
John.
- You guys remember John.
- Hi.
Listen, why don't John and I
go get a drink at the bar?
Sure.
Great, we'll be right back.
Come on, buddy.
It's an old sweater?
This house is unbelievable.
Haven't you been here before?
What do you mean?
You know,
when you and Rex were...
No. That was at work.
You guys did it in the office?
Yeah. Where?
In the men's room.
My God.
Why?
Where did you sleep with him?
Here.
Sorry.
It was in the handicapped stall,
so it was nicer than
the regular stalls.
This is Wade Boggs'
autographed bat.
I just barely
outbid Phil Donahue for that at auction.
Wow, cool.
Yeah, cool.
These boxing gloves were
worn by Joe Louis in his first fight.
This is art. Get it?
These were
John Lennon's glasses.
They're worth,
like, a million dollars.
That's me and Tom Skerritt.
Check this out.
It's Lance Armstrong's nut.
I had it
freeze-dried and bronzed.
Every now and then
when my life's
getting me down
and things are tough,
I just come up here
and I look at it.
And it reminds me that
things aren't so bad.
Sometimes you feel like a nut.
Sometimes you don't.
So, talk to me, Johnny Quest. How
are things with you and Lori?
Things are great, actually.
That's great. That is great.
You know,
Lori would hate me for saying this,
but she told me how
you are at the office.
And, as one gentleman
to another, I just want to say
I really hope
you fucking get Lou Gehrig's disease.
I think I need to
clear the air here a little.
Yeah, I'm kind of
a fun-time boss and what-not.
But, look, man,
I do that with everybody at the office.
I'm a kook.
I have no designs
on your girlfriend.
We work together, and that's it.
I think you're a great guy
and she's a very lucky girl.
Well, that's good to hear.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Hey, Ted.
Johnny, where are you?
You got to get over here, man.
Why, what's going on?
Okay, so I'm having
a little impromptu thing
with some people
at my apartment.
And, John, Sam Jones is here.
What?
Sam Jones.
Flash-fucking-Gordon is here.
Holy shit! What?
You remember I said my buddy's
cousin is friends with Sam Jones?
My buddy's in town
with his cousin,
and who do you
think is with him? Sam Jones.
Sam Jones is here, and, John,
his hair is
parted down the middle.
Just like in the movie.
Yes. Get over here right now.
Fuck, I can't!
I'm with Lori here.
I'm already on probation.
I can't.
John, Flash Gordon was the most important
influence of our formative years.
He taught us
right from wrong, good from evil.
And that the word
"acting" apparently
has an extremely
broad definition.
Flash Gordon is the symbol
of our friendship, John.
Come share this with me.
I'm coming.
Rex, I got to go.
I'll be back in 30 minutes,
tops, okay?
But Lori cannot find out.
She absolutely cannot know I was gone.
If you can cover for me,
I'm cool with all that other shit.
I got your back on this.
She won't know. I've been there.
All right,
this is one man to another.
I don't really know you,
but I'm trusting you, as a man.
This is serious.
Dude, one man to another.
I got you on this.
Thank you. I'll be back.
I'm going to have sex
with your girlfriend.
Johnny, thank Christ
you made it.
Dude, I got 10 minutes.
Where's Flash Gordon?
Okay, get ready.
Hey, Sam, this is the guy
I was telling you about.
Flash!
A-
Saviour of the universe!
Flash!
A-
He'll save every one of us!
Just a man with a man's courage.
He knows nothing but a man.
But he can never fail.
No one but the pure in heart
Can find the golden grail.
How you doing? Good to meet you.
I thank you for
saving every one of us.
Well, you're welcome.
He acknowledged it.
Let's do some shots.
With you?
My God, yes! My God, yes!
Let's go!
Thanks, Flash.
There you go, my friend.
Thank you.
Death to Ming!
Yes!
You know,
you guys seem pretty cool.
You like to party?
Cocaine, right?
Come on, dudes.
Don't tell me you never done it before.
Not recently, no.
I thought that was just
for people in Florida.
You better follow me.
Come on.
Johnny, I'm frightened.
We are going to
party like the '80s.
Show us how, Flash.
It's easy.
We just gotta nail
a lot of girls named Stephanie.
God, Johnny,
I got so much energy.
We better start
doing stupid shit.
Look, Johnny,
if we're ever going to
get serious about
opening a restaurant
we got to start planning it now.
Italian. Italian, yes.
What's
the special on Tuesdays? Eggplant parm.
Chopped salad, half price.
And it's a non-restricted place.
Yeah. What do you mean?
Anybody can come.
Of course. Jews are welcome.
Well, yeah.
Why wouldn't they be?
Exactly, that's what I'm saying.
Why even bring that up?
You don't bring it up,
you just let them in.
Why mention it? No one will.
Why are we talking about it?
You're talking about it.
I'm just saying, let them in.
Let them in. Right. Okay.
Exactly. Good.
No Mexicans, though.
This is how
everybody sang in the '90s.
Trust me, I can do this.
Shut up.
Let him try it, man.
All right, fuck it.
Go, go, go!
You son of a bitch!
Well, you never
should have trusted me. I'm on drugs.
Hey, Johnny,
I just had a great idea.
Let's go get drunk
and puke on cars from the overpass.
Come on, I do not sound
that much like Peter Griffin.
You can do any '90s
song with just vowels.
See? There, proof.
Garfield's eyes look like a pair of tits.
You were right.
If you can punch through this wall,
you really are Flash Gordon.
Are you going to do it?
I'm going to punch through it.
Come on, Sam, do it! Do it!
My God!
Yes! He did it!
What the hell you problem?
You break my wall!
I break you wall!
Break his arm off!
We're going to die.
We're all going to die.
Break this up, break this up.
Get him!
You break my wall!
This my home long time.
You break my wall,
you bastard men.
We're sorry,
it was an accident, okay?
I try to make duck dinner,
now plaster everywhere.
Chill out. Can we just talk about this?
What's your name? I'm John.
My name is Wan Ming.
Ming?
You pay many dollar for wall!
This bullshit!
This all bullshit!
Death to Ming!
Rape!
Sam, let him go.
You crazy! You crazy, man!
Come on, James Franco.
You pay for wall!
Move, sucker!
Greatest night ever!
Hey.
Hey, Guy.
What's going on?
This is Jared.
He's the guy who beat me up.
And we're in love.
Turns out I'm gay, or whatever.
I had no idea.
Hey, Jared,
let's go grab another one of these.
How we doing, ace?
You coming down?
Yeah, I don't feel so good.
Give it a couple of hours.
You'll be golden, Ponyboy.
You want a Xanax?
Holy shit. My God.
What?
I got to go.
Lori, I...
Lori!
Lori, wait, please.
Look, I'm sorry, I messed up...
John, I need you
out of the apartment tonight.
Can I...
Just give me the car keys.
Can I please just explain? No.
Look, I was...
I have given up
a huge chunk of my life for you.
I was going to stop in for like five
minutes and then Flash Gordon...
Just give me the car keys.
Lori.
Lori, please, I love you.
Johnny, there you are.
I had to get some air.
That guy from your office
is in there on the couch
making out with that
Van Wilder-looking guy.
You know what? Fuck you.
I don't even want to talk to you.
What?
Do you know what just happened?
Do you have any clue?
My fucking life just ended!
Come on. She'll go home,
she'll watch
Bridget Jones-something-asshole.
She'll have a good cry, she'll be fine.
You'll talk to her tomorrow.
Come on upstairs.
Are you even listening to me?
Do you give any shred of a shit?
Of course I do, Johnny.
"Thunder buddies
for life," remember?
Jesus! Lori was right.
I should have stopped hanging
out with you a long time ago.
I'm never going to
have a life with you around.
I'm 35 years old
and I'm going nowhere.
All I do is smoke pot and watch
movies with a teddy-fucking-bear.
Because of that,
I just lost the love of my life.
Johnny, I'm...
I'm sorry.
I gotta be on my own, Ted.
I can't see you anymore.
John, wait. Listen.
I love you!
So, word
through the grapevine is that you're
newly solo.
Rex, I have a lot of
work I need to get to.
I have tickets to Norah Jones
at the Hatch Shell tonight
and I would love it
if you would go with me.
You're asking me out
a week after I broke up with somebody?
Look, I'm going to
cut the shit, here.
Please.
This is the first time
that you've been single
in all the years
you've worked here.
Just go out with me one time.
And if you're miserable
and you hate it
then I promise I will never
even hint at the subject again.
Please.
Rex, I don't think it's smart.
I'm an asshole, I know that.
It worked for me in high school,
and it's been
a reflex ever since.
Lori, the worst that can happen
is that you go on
a fun, casual date
with a guy who
just wants a chance
to prove that he can be
something more than a jerk.
Plus, you are a huge catch.
And it's about time
someone treated you that way.
Fuck it. Fine.
Fine. It sure as hell
beats crying myself to sleep every night.
And if that means
getting you off my back,
well, that's just a bonus.
I'll pick you up at 8:00.
Johnny. It's me.
Go away.
Johnny, open the door,
please, I want to talk.
Jesus Christ!
What the fuck, man?
Sorry. Look, Johnny,
I know you're pissed, all right?
But just listen to me
for five seconds.
I saw Lori leaving
the apartment with Rex.
What?
I'm serious, John.
I went over to talk to her
and maybe take some
of the heat off you.
And there he was,
picking her up.
They were going
to the Hatch Shell.
You're fucking unbelievable,
you know that?
How stupid do you think I am?
If you think that by
making shit like that up
you're going to make me
choose some kind of loyalty to you
over her you're out
of your fucking mind.
Johnny, it's the truth,
I'm telling you.
You know what? Get out of here.
You know what?
You're acting like a cock. You know that?
What? I'm acting like a cock?
Yes, you are.
So shut your meat hole
for a second and listen to me.
Meat hole? What?
That's not right, is it? No.
"Pudding hole"?
Is that what they say?
No, it can't be that either.
Because, "How can you have any
pudding if you don't eat your meat?"
Right? Pink Floyd.
Look, the point is,
you're blaming me
for something that
you did to yourself.
Lori was right about you.
You cannot take responsibility for
anything that goes on in your life.
And you can?
I don't have to.
I'm a fucking teddy bear.
You know something? I didn't tie
you up and drag you to that party.
I wanted you to come
because you're supposedly my best friend.
You can't stand there
and tell me
that you haven't always seen Lori
as a threat to our friendship.
It works out
so much better for you
when you and I are
getting fucked up
on the couch
at 9:00 A.M., doesn't it?
Listen to yourself.
What am I?
Emperor Ming, here, controlling your mind?
That's your choice, John.
And by blaming me,
you, you're just
making yourself
look like a pussy.
Sometimes I think back to
that Christmas morning
when I was eight years old.
I wish I had just
gotten a Teddy Ruxpin.
Say that one more time.
Teddy Rux-fucking-pin!
Shit!
Fuck, man!
Fuck! Cocksucker!
Fucking stop! Fuck!
Why are you crying?
My dick is squished by the TV.
I'm so sorry, Johnny.
So am I, man.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Listen.
You got to let me help you
make things right with you and Lori.
There's no
putting things right. She fucking hates me.
No, John. We can get her back.
Look,
you remember when you were 10,
and you hit that squirrel
with your BB gun?
And then when we saw
it fall from the tree,
we both started crying,
you remember?
And then we ran up to it
and we tried to give it CPR,
and it came back to life.
John, we could do that again.
Ted,
we crushed its ribcage and blew out
its lungs trying to give it CPR.
It died.
Come on. We're going
to the Hatch Shell.
Yeah!
Thanks. We're going to take a short
break, but we'll be back in a few.
Play Chopsticks, you jazzy slut.
Teddy!
How are you?
How are you doing,
you fuzzy little asshole?
Well, I'm not a hot,
half-Muslim chick
who sold 37 million records,
but I'm hanging in there.
Half-Indian, but thanks.
Yeah, whatever. Thanks for 9/11.
Listen, I want you to
meet a good pal of mine, all right?
John Bennett, Norah Jones.
Hi, Norah Jones.
Hey, there, sweaty.
You ready to
bring down the house?
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you for the opportunity, Miss...
Ma'am Jones. Thank you.
Jesus, you look fantastic.
Well, you're probably
not used to seeing me fully clothed.
I know, I mean, me and Norah met
back in 2002 at this event for
this charity that we
were both involved with.
This wonderful charity,
actually, for kids
who'd been fucked
by a family member.
And we... We ended up
hooking up in the back room.
Actually, you weren't so bad
for a guy with no penis.
You know, I have written
so many angry letters to Hasbro about that.
Thank you.
Now, I'm going to
give my chops a rest
and bring a friend up
to the stage.
He's going to
sing a song to a special lady
in the audience
who he loves very much.
Please give a big hand
to John Bennett.
My God.
Holy shit!
I gotta fuck her again.
Hi, my name is John Bennett,
and this is for Lori Collins.
Because I love you.
This song always reminds me
of the most important night of my life.
The night we met.
This is the theme song
from the movie Octopussy.
ALL I wanted
was a sweet distraction For an hour or two.
Had no intention to do.
Still better than Katy Perry.
Funny how it
always goes with love.
When you don't look, you find.
But then we're two of a kind.
We move as one.
We're an all time high.
You suck, get off the stage!
Come on. Give him a chance.
Doing so much more.
You're an asshole!
Than falling...
Jesus!
Someone call an ambulance!
That was insane.
Did you see the way
the guy's body hit the ground?
He was like a rag doll.
Yeah, I'd rather
just not talk about it.
Do you want to go
get a drink after this?
I feel like I could
use one after seeing a guy almost die.
No, I think I'd
rather just have you take me home.
One drink. Come on.
No, not really feeling up to it.
All right, I get it.
And, you know,
I don't blame you.
I mean, when you think about it,
it was actually really unfair of
him to embarrass you like that.
Just to be clear,
I'm not embarrassed.
Listen, John and I may have our
problems, but at least he tried.
You know what? I don't feel
like talking to you about this.
Where are you going?
Taking a cab. I'm going home.
Finally.
Down here.
Not looking up your towel.
Swear to God.
Not looking at your funny business.
Ted, what are you doing here?
I need to talk to you.
Listen, if you're here to fight
John's battles for him...
Look, just let me
talk first, all right?
And then you can
say whatever you want.
Look, John loves you very much,
more than anything in the world,
and he's falling
to fucking pieces without you.
He knows he screwed up huge
but you've got to believe me,
it wasn't all his fault.
I told him to bail on you
that night at Rex's and he said, "No."
He said "no," he was going to stay there
with you, and I twisted his arm, Lori.
So, if you just give him
one more chance.
I promise I will leave
and I'll never come back.
All right? He'll be all yours.
Ted, that's a really nice offer,
but I don't want you to do that.
This is between John and me
and I don't think it can be fixed.
Yeah, because of me!
Look, Lori,
you want him to be a man.
But as long as
he's got his teddy bear,
he's always going to be a boy.
He's waiting down
at Charlie's right now.
So, if you go down there
and just talk to him
I'll be gone when you get back.
Forever.
And, you'll see,
he'll never be
scared of thunder again.
"Michelob Ultra
Tuscan Orange Grapefruit."
My God, America is imploding.
Hi, Ted.
Fuck!
Lori, what...
Hey.
What are you doing here?
You can thank Ted.
Should I sit?
Yeah, if you want.
Okay.
So, work's good?
Everything good, there?
Yeah. Yeah, work's good.
I guess we can't make
small talk all day?
If it's okay with you,
I just want to say what I want to say.
I could sit here and
tell you I'm sorry,
it was a huge misunderstanding,
and I'm ready to change,
but I don't think you want
to hear any of that crap.
I'm not going
to try to get you to take me back.
Why would you?
I've been a really shitty boyfriend
for the last four years.
I don't deserve you.
I know I didn't take
our relationship seriously but, Lori,
I do love you more
than life itself.
All I want is...
I just want to end on good terms.
I owe that to you.
I want you to be happy.
You deserve that.
And I just hope that
maybe we can still be friends.
Thank you for being so honest.
That's pretty much it.
Thanks for coming by.
Whoa!
Yeah, as you can see
you've been
a part of our family for quite some time.
Welcome home.
Yeah,
it's kind of funny, actually.
I got a lot of pictures of
you guys at my house.
Is he all mine, Daddy?
Yes, he is,
my little winner. Yes, he is.
Ted, you've arrived
at a lucky time.
It's almost Robert's play hour.
Yeah, I'm guessing you guys
don't have a PS3.
I'm guessing you're more of a "wooden
horse with a wig" kind of family.
Yeah.
No. Yeah. No.
Yeah, see, there's the guy.
Now, Ted, you belong
to Robert now, okay? You do as he says.
You think you're just
going to get away with a kidnapping?
That's a nice
fucking example you're setting...
Language!
Sorry. Sorry.
You know, Ted,
when I was a little boy,
I saw you on television.
And I thought you were
the most amazing,
most wonderful thing
I'd ever seen. Ever.
And I asked my dad if I could have
a magical little teddy bear, too.
And he said, "No."
Can you just email me
the rest of this story?
And I was so heartbroken.
And I promised myself that
if I ever had a son,
I would never,
ever, ever say no to him.
Ever.
Maybe "no" to a Snickers bar
every once in a while wouldn't hurt.
Me and Ted are going
to be best friends, Daddy.
Yes, you are,
my little chipmunk.
Happy playtime.
Jesus fucking Christ!
I said a bad word one time.
Daddy punished me for it.
That's a great story.
I felt like I was there.
Daddy gave me an ouch.
Now, I have to give you an ouch.
All right, kid, you win.
We'll do it your way.
What do you want to do?
You want to play a game?
It's playtime, right?
We'll play a game.
Yeah, I want to play a game.
Good, good.
Let's see. How about we...
How about we play
a little game of hide and seek?
I love hide and seek. I'll hide.
Now, hang on a sec, there.
Your dad likes you to show good manners.
Right, Tubby McFat-Fuck?
Okay. You hide first.
Great. Fantastic.
Okay, now you count to 100,
and then you try to find me, okay?
Okay.
Do I need to wash my hands
before I play this game?
No. That's a weird
fucking question. No, just start counting.
One, two,
three, four, five,
No peeking, now,
or you'll get kid cancer.
Eight, nine, ten,
eleven, twelve, thirteen...
Hey.
You walking home alone?
Yeah.
Do you need a lift?
I'm okay.
If I get raped,
it'll be my fault for what I'm wearing.
Listen, John.
There's something
that I need to say to you, too.
Hey. Hey.
John, I hope that...
Listen, I don't want
you to think that...
Sorry.
I want us to keep talking
because I think that maybe...
Go ahead.
Whoever this is,
it's not a good time.
John, it's me. Can you hear me?
Ted? Listen,
I got to call you back.
No, John, don't hang up!
I'm in trouble.
What do you mean?
What kind of trouble?
They got me.
That freaky guy from the park,
and that kid who I
think is his son,
but may also be his lover,
I don't know.
Whoa, whoa, slow down.
Where are you?
I'm not sure, it's...
Hello? Hello, John?
Hello?
You're not a very
polite guest, are you?
Shit!
Ted, hello? Ted?
What's the matter? Ls he okay?
I don't know. Where is he?
I don't know. He just
said he was in trouble.
Can you call him back?
No, it's blocked.
Wait a second.
Go. Take Columbus to Herald
and get on the expressway.
You put us in
quite a pickle here.
We have to go now.
Yeah. Good idea.
You F-ing A-hole.
We tried to make do
with other teddy bears,
but none of them were you, Ted.
Hello, 911?
I need the police right away.
This guy took my teddy bear.
Hello?
Let me out of here,
you crazy bastard!
I hear the fat kid running.
I bet it's hilarious.
Let me out of here!
I am a citizen of
the United States of America
and I have rights!
Robert, seatbelt.
It should be
right here, somewhere.
Johnny!
Whoa, whoa! Stop, stop!
That's them, turn around!
Stay with them.
Hang on!
Back off, Susan Boyle!
My God!
He's going to jump! Get closer.
All right, easy. Come on, Ted.
Shit! Yes!
Hey, Johnny!
Total T.J. Hooker, right?
Yes! Fucking-A right!
Shit!
Go! Go! Go!
Daddy!
Let's see how well
you know these streets.
Where is he?
Jesus!
There he is. Pull over.
Where?
No!
You can't have my teddy bear!
Holy shit.
Sorry.
Somebody had to
go Joan Crawford on that kid.
Come on.
Ted?
My God!
Shit!
Jesus.
Stay here.
Just stay there! No, John!
You're mine, Ted!
Screw you, pal.
I belong to John Bennett.
But I can give you love,
and rocking horses,
and dancing.
I think we're very
far apart on this.
Ted! Johnny!
My God!
Ted!
John.
Lori, get the stuffing.
Get it all.
Johnny.
You're going to
be okay, buddy. Do you understand?
You're going to be fine.
Jesus, I look like
the robot from Aliens.
No, look at me, buddy.
I promise,
you're going to be okay.
I don't think so. I'm...
I'm in trouble.
I need...
I need to tell you something.
What is it?
Don't ever lose her again.
She's the most important...
the most
important part of your life.
Even more than me.
She's your thunder buddy now.
She's...
I got it.
Baby, I don't know if
this is going to work.
Please, just try.
Come on, buddy.
I'm so sorry.
You did everything you could.
Ted!
I'm alive, Johnny!
My God!
I'm alive.
Your magical wish worked!
You're back!
Yeah, I mean,
when you sewed me up
you put some of the stuffing
in the wrong places
so I'm a little fucked up.
But will you take care of me
forever and ever?
I'm just
kidding you. I thought it would be funny
if you thought
I was fucking retarded.
You asshole!
Come here, you bastard.
Welcome back, Ted.
It was you.
You did it.
Son of a bitch!
You wished for my life back.
No. No.
I wished for my life back.
I love you.
I love you, too.
And I want you to know that,
after last night
I don't ever want to lose
anyone who matters to me ever again.
I'm not going to
wait any longer for my life to start.
Lori,
will you marry me?
All I ever wanted
was you, John Bennett.
And so John, Lori and
Ted lived happily ever after.
Having discovered at last,
that all they really needed was each other.
John and Lori were
married in Cambridge
by a very special
Justice of the Peace.
By the power vested in me
by the New York Jets
and by the united peoples
of the planet Mongo,
I now pronounce
you man and wife.
You may kiss the bride, Johnny.
Hi. Tom Skerritt.
Tom Skerritt! Wow!
Thanks so much for coming.
My daughter better be alive,
you sick son of a bitch.
I am so fake-happy for her.
You know, Sam,
there's only one way to end a perfect day.
What's that?
Flash jump.
Right.
One, two, three!
Yeah!
And that's the story
of how one magical wish
forever changed the lives
of three very special friends.
Ted and Tami-Lynn continued their
torrid love affair for quite some time.
One afternoon,
Ted was caught behind the deli counter
eating potato salad
off of Tami-Lynn's bare bottom.
He was instantly
promoted to store manager.
Sam Jones moved
back to Hollywood
with the goal of
restarting his film career.
He currently resides in Burbank
where he shares
a studio apartment
with his roommate,
Brandon Routh.
Remember Brandon Routh
from that God-awful Superman movie?
Jesus Christ!
Thanks for getting our hopes up
and taking a giant shit on us.
Rex was forced to give up
his pursuit of Lori.
Not long afterwards,
he fell into a deep depression
and died of
Lou Gehrig's disease.
Donny was arrested
by Boston police
and charged with
kidnapping a plush toy.
The charges were dropped
when everyone realized
how completely stupid
that sounded.
Robert got a trainer,
lost a substantial amount of weight
and went on to become
Taylor Lautner.